Tony Manero knows the old days are over. But nobody's
gonna tell him he can't feel that good again.
Staying Alive is a drama, music film directed by Sylvester Stallone.
It's five years later and Tony Manero's Saturday Night Fever is still burning.
Now he's strutting toward his biggest challenger yet -
making it as a dancer on the Broadway stage.
Tony Manero, played by John Travolta.
Jackie, played by Cynthia Rhodes.
Laura, played by Finola Hughes.
Jesse, played by Steve Inwood.
Mrs. Manero, played by Julie Bovasso.
Butler, played by Charles Ward.
Staying Alive is a 1983 American dance drama film and the
sequel to Saturday Night Fever (1977).
It was directed by Sylvester Stallone, produced by Stallone and the Saturday Night
Fever producer Robert Stigwood, and written by Stallone and Norman Wexler.
It stars John Travolta, reprising his Saturday Night Fever role as Tony Manero, with Cynthia
Rhodes, Finola Hughes, Joyce Hyser, Julie Bovasso, Viktor Manoel and Kevyn Morrow.
The title comes from the Bee Gees song of the same name, which was used as the theme song to
Saturday Night Fever and is played during the final scene of Staying Alive.
Theatrically released on July 15, 1983, Staying Alive received negative reviews.
It earned $127 million worldwide on a $22 million budget.
It featured the song "Far from Over" by Stallone's brother Frank Stallone,
which reached #10 on the Billboard Hot 100 and the Cashbox charts.
The film explores themes of career, dancing master, nightclub, disco, broadway.
The tone is emotional.